Kunal ji and Rakesh, first
tell me the price of their 10th class ticket, which one have
you heard today, hey,
this is our buy opinion
and we have to buy ICICI Lombard, on which
we have a buy opinion, this top has been there for a long
time, for about one and a half to two months, we have been
seeing consolidation in it and now we
feel that it is fully ready to
give the next move, it is
sitting in a shape for the medium to long term, on the top, so let's
buy heavily on looting for the medium term and long term, that product is
a part better in technical structure,
in good condition, what is the special
thing, it is Martin and Shetty and the
targets are quite high, so here
we will be in the player's corner for two targets, the
first target is 1750, the first target is 1750, the
second target is 1999, for both these
targets, we are buying ICICI Lombard on the
decline on this side, the
in-charge of Jhaal rent is
seen coming for ICICI Lombard, for you at
this time from Kunal ji and Rakesh  Keep it for six months